[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2004, a National Geographic article foretold the formation of the flood that devastated New Orleans after Hurricane Katrina.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of these snakes produce venom, lethal to humans.  Which one does not?", "correct_answer": "Desert Kingsnake", "incorrect_answers": ["King Cobra", "Mamba", "Rattlesnake"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Stinging nettle has a large number of medicinal properties. What vitamin, essential for blood clotting, does fresh stinging nettle contain in large amounts?", "correct_answer": "Vitamin K", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin B12", "Vitamin A", "Vitamin D"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fleas can jump 130 times their own height.", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the general term used for the food that is forbidden by the Jewish dietary laws?", "correct_answer": "Treif", "incorrect_answers": ["Dores", "Zefek", "Kosher"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jennifer Tilly starred in the 1982 horror movie One Dark Night with Adam West.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors was not a student of  Stella Adler?", "correct_answer": "Eli Wallach", "incorrect_answers": ["Warren Beatty", "Robert DeNiro", "Martin Sheen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A hairless Chinese Crested dog needs to be protected from which of the following?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Sunburn", "Winter Wind", "Dry Skin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All other things being equal, which 3-card meld is more likely to be increased to a 4-card meld in the game gin rummy?", "correct_answer": "Eight Nine Ten of Diamonds", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack Queen King of Hearts", "Three Kings", "Ace Two Three of Spades"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What price did someone pay for Marilyn Monroes bra that she wore in the 1959 movie Some Like It Hot?", "correct_answer": "$14,000", "incorrect_answers": ["$4,000", "$10,000", "$1,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When she modeled as a teenager, Angelina Jolie appeared in a music video of this artist.", "correct_answer": "Lenny Kravitz", "incorrect_answers": ["Sting", "Bryan Adams", "Chris Isaak"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All of the following actors starred in all the three Blade movies: Stephen Dorf, Traci Lords, Ron Perlman, Parker Posey, Kris Kristofferson.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]